I'll let you go first. I'll do worse.
Hit them where it hit them where it
hurts. Leave you in the dirt. Put in
work. Hit them where. Hit them where it
hurts.
Hit them where it hurts. Hit
it with her. You won't act right. We
active at sun today. This ain't no cat.
We b
Okay, what you going to do? Make your
move. Reverse you. No round two. Been
waiting on halftime. It's over. Stay
sidelines away. Hey, we ain't never
going to stop. We ain't never going to
back down. Going to take it to the top.
Going to leave you in the background.
Give it all. Give it all we go. Eyes are
on this now.
Take a shot. Take a shot. We going 5 4 3
2 I let you go first. I'll do worse. Hit
them where. Hit them where it hurts.
Leave you in the dirt. Putting work. Hit
Hit them where hurts.
Hit them where hurts. I'll let you go
first. I'll do worse. Hit him where
hurts. Leave you in the dirt. Put in
work. Hit him where. Hit him where it
hurts.
Hit him where it hurts.
Hit him where it hurts. I'm a lot to
handle. I don't think that you can
handle it. Last one tried to blame me.
Go. Hey, ask them how they manage it.
I'm too bus. Yeah, it's going to cost
you. No, you don't want nothing.
We ain't never going to stop. We ain't
never going to back down. Going to take
it to the top. Going to leave you in the
background. Give it all. Give it all we
go. Eyes are on the Take a shot. Take a
show. We go. You fight for three. I'll
let you go first. I'll do worse. Had
them where it hurts. Leave you in the
dirt. Put in work. Hit them where it
hurts.
Hit them where it hurts.
Hit them where hurts. I let you go
first. I'll do worse. Hit them right.
Hit them where hurts. Leave you in the
dark. Putting work. Hit them where. Hit
them where.
Hit them where
it hurts.